http://www.ostari.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
BY VISITING OSTARI.COM (“SITE”), YOU ARE CONSENTING TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY.
The date of this Privacy Policy is July 12, 2018.
This Privacy Policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) is used online. Please read our Privacy Policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
The terms “we,” “us,” and “our” refers to Ostari.com. The terms “user,” “you,” and “your” refer to Site visitors, customers, and any other users of the Site.
The term “personal information” is defined as information that you voluntarily provide to us that personally identifies you and/or your contact information, such as your name, phone number, and email address.
Use of ostari.com, including all materials presented herein and all online services provided by Ostari, is subject to the following Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all Site visitors, customers, and all other users of the Site. By using the Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy, without modification, and acknowledge reading it.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?
When ordering or registering on our Site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number, company name or other details to help you with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our Site.
Information Gathering and Usage
When you register for ostari.com, we ask for information such as your name, email address, and credit card information. Members who sign up for the free account are not required to enter a name or credit card.
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the Site, or use certain other Site features. Ostari.com uses collected information for the following general purposes: providing products and services, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contacting you, and research. Ostari may also use collected information to administer a contest, promotion, survey or other Site feature or to send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
How do we protect your information?
We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.
For your convenience we may store your credit card information longer than 60 days in order to expedite future orders, and to automate the billing process.
Do we use “cookies”?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a Site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the Site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
Cookies are required to use the Ostari service. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, keep track of advertisements, and compile aggregate data about Site traffic and Site interactions. We may also use trusted third-party services to track this information on our behalf. Cookies are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current Site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about Site traffic and Site interaction so that we can offer better Site experiences and tools in the future. You are required to re-login to your Ostari.com account after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If you turn cookies off, some of the features that make your Site experience more efficient may not function properly. It won't affect the user's experience that make your Site experience more efficient and may not function properly.
Third-party disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.
Third-party links
The Site may contain links to third party websites. Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on our Site. Other sites accessible through our site via links or otherwise have their own policies in regard to privacy. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third parties.
Google
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our Site in order to provide a positive user experience. We have implemented Google Display Network Impression Reporting, Demographics and Interests Reporting, and DoubleClick Platform Integration.
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles at: https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/6008942?hl=en%20.&visit_id=1-636670270129583388-3758542982&rd=1
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our Site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.
We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out of Google Advertisement Services
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. You can learn more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
In accordance with CalOPPA, users can visit our site anonymously. Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.
How does our Site handle Do Not Track signals?
We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
In the event that you enable or send a “Do Not Track” signal or similar mechanism relating to the tracking of browsing activities, please note that Ostari.com does not have practices or protocols in place to honor or respond to such requests. Ostari.com, however, only collects the types of information otherwise described in this Online Privacy Policy.
Third-party behavioral tracking
It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
Our Sites and Services do not target and are not intended to attract children under the age of 13. Ostari does not knowingly solicit Personal Information from children under the age of 13 or send them requests for Personal Information.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur we will notify you via email within 7 business days.
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to, send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions, market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.
To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:
Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.
Access/ Accuracy
To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, Ostari wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. In those circumstances where we collect Personal Information from you on our Sites, our goal is to provide a means of contacting Ostari should you need to review, update or correct that Personal Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information by email to service@ostari.com and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.
Your Consent
By using our Sites and Services, you consent to the terms of this Online Privacy Policy and to Ostari’s processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where Ostari collects Personal Information on the Sites.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Ostari reserves the right to change this Online Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the Online Privacy Policy will govern our use of your Personal Information. Accordingly, should this Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our Sites and Services for a reasonable period of time. By continuing to access or use Ostari’s Sites and Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Online Privacy Policy.
Unsubscribe
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at sales@ostari.com and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us using the information below.
ostari.com
761 University Ave.
Los Gatos, CA 95032
United States
ops@ostari.com
(800) 748-6399
Last Edited on 2018-05-18
Contact
Ostari, Inc.
$$$
761 University Ave., Suite DLos Gatos, CA 95032
+1 (800) 748-6399
+1 (800) 748-6399
Fax: 408-402-5074
Latest Articles8 New Features of Microsoft 365May 18th, 2018Most Talked About IT Certifications for 2018March 28th, 2018Social Media LinkedInRSS Feed
News Flash Alerts
Receive Tech Briefs about the most current breaches, useful tools and more.
Name*Email*
PhoneCompanyBy clicking Submit, you agree to the Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy.PhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
© Copyright 2020 Ostari, Inc.
Privacy Policy | Terms and Conditions
This site uses cookies in order to improve your experience with us. By using the site or by dismissing this pop-up you’re consenting to their use.
More Information ContinuePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
